Guide to the Records of American Association for Ethiopian Jews (AAEJ), undated, 1960-1961, 1963, 1965-1968, 1970-1995, 2001-2002 *I-503
American Jewish Historical Society, Boston, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup I: American Association for Ethiopian Jews (AAEJ), undated, 1973-1994; Boxes 1-37.
  - Series B: AAEJ General Files, undated, 1979-1994; Box 4, Folder 12 -- Box 11, Folder 18.
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council, undated, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress (NCEC), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress (NCEC), undated, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Operation Moses and Operation Joshua, 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Susan Pollack, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Postal Stuff, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Program to train Ethiopian Jewish Immigrants in Israel as Teachers, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Request for humanitarian assistance towards unification of Ethiopian Jews with their families, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Rescue Campaign, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Rescue/Relief Report, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Rescue - Small Scale, Steve Brownstein, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Rescue of Ethiopian Jews, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Situation of Ethiopian children in Israel, undated, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "Soviet Jewish Emigration to Israel," by Roberta Cohen, June 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Stuff for Will Recant and Anita, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Sudan/Winnipeg Meeting October 6, 1986, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Unfinished Exodus" film subtitles, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Vigil at Knesset, family reunification (see OS6F Folder 1), undated, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Youth Aliyah, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Zimmerman, Marvin, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Series C: AAEJ Washington, D.C., undated, 1973-1974, 1976-1993; Box 12, Folder 1 -- Box 26, Folder 9.
    Arranged into two subseries.
    The series contains files mainly of the AAEJ office in Washington, D.C. This series consists of two subseries: AAEJ Washington DC General Office Files and Individual Files.
    - Subseries 1: General Office Files, undated, 1974, 1976-1977, 1979-1992; Box 12, Folder 1 -- Box 20, Folder 14.
      The subseries contains the general office files of the AAEJ office in Washington, D.C. Items of interest to researchers of the AAEJ are the AAEJ board mailings, organizational history, and lists of board members. The subseries also consists of files of "other Ethiopian Jewry organizations" listed alphabetically (see Box 15, Folder 6 to Box 18, Folder 10). The subseries is also composed of the files of Private Volunteer Organizations (see Box 19, Folders 1-9). Also included are files pertaining to the AAEJ's involvement in the rescue effort (see Box 19, Folders 10 to Box 20, Folder 3).
      - AAEJ Board Mailings, 1982-1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - AAEJ Board Mailings, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - AAEJ Conference, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - AAEJ: Direct Mail Fall '86 Newsletter (NCEC) and Letters to Nate re: Cranston solicitation, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - AAEJ: Direct Mail NCEC, undated, 1984-1987, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - AAEJ: FR BGVR - Draft of Letter, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - AAEJ: Fundraising Federation Donors, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - AAEJ: Fundraising Thank You Form Letters, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - AAEJ Newsline, undated, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - AAEJ: Organizational History, undated, 1983, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - AAEJ: Will Recant presentations to Jewish Federations, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Agency for International Development, 1987-1988, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Anita Moss' packet from AAEJ Board Meeting: November 8, 1987, undated, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Beth Israel Organization of Ethiopian Jewish Immigrants, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - BGVR 100+, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Board Meeting, October 1990, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Board Members, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Board Members, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Board Members, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Board Members, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Budget/Expenses, 1983, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Call to Conscience 1989, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Camp Ibenat (Gonder), Expulsions from Refugee Camp, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Congress: Ethiopian Sanctions Legislation, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Congress: Resolutions, undated, 1983-1984, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Congress - State Department: Correspondence, undated, 1983-1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Congress - State Department: Human Rights Reports: Ethiopia, undated, 1983-1985, 1987, 1989, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Congressional Hearings, undated, 1982, 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Congressional Human Rights Caucus, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Ethiopia: Famine, General (see OS6F Folder 1), 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Ethiopia: Famine, General, undated, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Ethiopia: Famine, Gonder, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Ethiopia: Famine, Locusts, undated, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Ethiopia: Famine, Relief and Rehabilitation Commission, undated, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Ethiopian Government, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Ethiopia: Jewish Villages, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Family Reunification Process, circa 1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Financial statements, 6 months ending June 30, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - International Human Rights Law Group, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - IRS Forms, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Israel: Operation Solomon, undated, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Israel: United Israel Appeal, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Israel: Yemin Orde Educational Study, circa 1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Local Legislatures: Resolutions, 1983, 1985-1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Medical Insurance Forms, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - North American Conference on Ethiopian Jewry, undated, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - NY Fundraisers, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Operation Moses Remembrance, undated, 1984-1986, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Organization of African Unity, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - ORT, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Orthodox Rabbis for Ethiopian Jewry, undated, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Other EJ Organizations: AIPAC, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Anti Defamation League, 1985-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Aliyah Jewish Agency, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Jewish Committee, December 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Jewish Congress, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Jewish World Service (contains photograph), undated, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Rabbinic Network for Ethiopian Jewry, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Rabbinic Network for Ethiopian Jewry, undated, 1980, 1984-1986, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Rabbinic Network for Ethiopian Jewry, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Rabbinic Network for Ethiopian Jewry, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Other EJ Organizations: American Rabbinic Network for Ethiopian Jewry: Hinenu Project (contains photographs), undated, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Amnesty International, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Association for Ethiopian Immigrants, undated, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Australasian Union of Jewish Students, undated, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Other EJ Organizations: B'nai B'rith, undated, 1983-1984, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Boston JCC, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Canadian Association for Ethiopian Jews (see OS1F Folder 1), undated, 1983-1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Other EJ Organizatinos: Canadian Jewish Congress, 1984, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Canadian Physicians for Aid and Relief, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Congressional Caucus for Ethiopian Jewry, undated, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Congressional Caucus for Ethiopian Jewry - Wilson/Cranston/Boschwitz, undated, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Congressional Caucus for Ethiopian Jewry - Caucus, undated, 1988, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Congressional Caucus for Ethiopian Jewry - Congressional Human Rights Foundation, 1984, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Congressional Human Rights Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Conservative Rabbinic Assembly, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Defence for Children International, undated, 1986-1989, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Israel Rescue Committee for Ethiopian Jews, 1987, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Jewish Agency for Israel, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Jewish Community Council, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Jewish National Fund, undated, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, General, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Albany-Delmar, NY, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, JCRC Subcommittee on EJ(?), 1987 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Eugene, OR, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Miami, FL, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Michigan Association for EJs, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, San Diego Rescue Committee, undated, 1986, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Bergen, NJ(?), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Washington AEJ, undated, 1984, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Ethiopian Jewry Committee of Northern California, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Twin Cities Committees for Ethiopian Jews, 1984, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, New York, undated, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Organization for Ethiopian Jewry (CA), undated, 1984, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, Philadelphia (contains photograph), 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, San Diego, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Local American AAEJ Chapters, San Diego (see OS1F Folder 1), undated, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Other EJ Organizations: National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Noah's Ark, undated, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Other EJ Organizations: North American Conference on Ethiopian Jewry (NACOEJ), 1983-1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Other EJ Organizations: North American Conference on Ethiopian Jewry (NACOEJ), undated, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Resolutions, undated, 1982-1985, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Union of American Hebrew Congregations, undated, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Other EJ Organizations: Union of American Hebrew Congregations - Mazon, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Other EJ Organizations: United Jewish Appeal, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Other EJ Organizations: United Jewish Appeal, DC, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Other EJ Organizations: World Union of Jewish Students (contains photographs), undated, 1980, 1982-1983, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Packet from AAEJ Board Meeting: September 13, 1986, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Press: Lists, Releases, undated, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Bread for the World, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Catholic Relief Services, undated, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Concern, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Food for the Hungry, undated, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Grassroots International, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: InterAction, 1983, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Oxfam, undated, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: Red Cross (International), October 1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - PVO's (misc.) [Private Volunteer Organizations]: World Vision, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: "Back to Ethiopia", 1985, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: Checklist of All Methods, 1984, 1986, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: Individual Rescues/Stories, Prisoners of Zion, undated, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: Orphanage Project, undated, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: Program for EJ's in US with relatives in Ethiopia, undated, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: Sponsorship Project and Names, undated, 1982, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Rescue: AAEJ: Student Program, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Rescue: Ethiopian Jews in Sudan since end of Operation Moses, undated, 1980, 1983, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Rescue: Large Scale: Big Family Reunion Lists, undated, 1983-1989 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
      - Rescue: Large Scale: Big Family Reunion Lists: Special Project: List of names for members, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Rescue: Large Scale: Big Family Reunion Lists: List of villages and numbers, 1976, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Rescue: Large Scale: Lobbying in Israel, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Rescue: Small Scale: AAEJ Pilgrimage, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Rescue: Small Scale: AAEJ in Sudan, 1974, 1976-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Rescue: Small Scale: AAEJ in Sudan, undated, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Rescue: Small Scale: Already Rescued, undated, 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Rescue: Summit Meetings, AAEJ and other EJ groups, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Save All Ethiopian Jews, undated, 1986-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Special Board Meeting: June 30, 1991, undated, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - State Department: General, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Sudan: Internal Political Situation, undated, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Sudan: Prisoners, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Sudan: Refugee Crisis, Camp Conditions, undated, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Telex, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - United Nations, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - US Customs, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Visa application, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Work Papers, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Subseries 2: Individual Files, undated, 1973, 1977-1993; Box 21, Folder 1 -- Box 26, Folder 9.
      Arranged alphabetically by last name.
      The subseries consists of the individual files of those chiefly involved in the AAEJ rescue effort, arranged alphabetically by last name. The subseries contains their correspondence as well as the photographs of individuals.
      - Addisu, Messele, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Aghion-Saar, Irit, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Berger, Graenum, undated, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Bitew, Avi, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Boschwitz, Rudy, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Byaliss, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Charish, Howard, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Clinton, Bill, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Cohen, John (contains photographs), undated, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Cohen, Scott, undated, 1987-1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Dietz, Phyllis, undated, 1982, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Doctors (contains photographs), undated, 1981, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Donnelly Group, undated, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Eisenberg, Mira, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Eleazar, Rachamim, undated, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Etzion, Yehuda, undated, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Everett, Edith and Henry (1 of 2), 1979, 1982-1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Everett, Edith and Henry (2 of 2), undated, 1987-1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Feldman, Micha, undated, 1983-1985, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Fellman, Jane, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Feltman, David, 1973, 1977-1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Feltman, David, undated, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Goldstein, Rabbi Mordechai, undated, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Habteyes, Fekade, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Hadane (contains photograph), undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Harburger, Walter, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Hart, Paul, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Herz, Roger, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Hoch, Dov, undated, 1988-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hoffman, Charles, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Interns, undated, 1987-1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Jackson, Jesse, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Jackson, Peter, undated, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Jacobovici, Simcha, undated, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kaplan, Steve, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Kolodny, Danielle (contains 5¼ inch diskette), 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Kovler, Peter, undated, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Kraar, Marty, undated, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Kulick, Gil, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Kushner, Arlene, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Kushner, Arlene, undated, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Leeder, Sandy, undated, 1987, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Lenhoff, Howard, undated, 1985-1987, 1989, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Levin, Debra (contains photographs), undated, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Lichtenstein, Yona, 1991, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Lubrani, Uri, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Masters, Richard, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Migdal, Sheldon, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Miller, Joyce, undated, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Moliner, Jerry, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - ORT, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Ostrovsky, Tzachi, undated, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Peri, Chaim (contains photographs), 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Peri, Chaim, undated, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Pollack, Susan, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Recant, Will (contains photographs), undated, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Reinach, Jill, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Rosenberg, Henry, undated, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Rosenblatt, Lisa, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Rosenblatt, Lisa, undated, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Schachter, Hal, undated, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Schnapper, LaDena, undated, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Shapiro, Nate (contains photographs), undated, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Shapiro, Nate, undated, 1984-1985, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Sidofsky, Carol (contains photograph), undated, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Sislen, Buddy, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Sweet, Reisa (contains photographs), undated, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Weiner, Mark, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Westheimer, Dr. Ruth (contains photograph), undated, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Wolde-Mariam, Mesfin, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Yona, Issayas, undated, 1979, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Zeller, Jack, undated, 1980, 1982, 1985, 1988-1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Zucker, Daniel, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Series D: AAEJ Articles, undated, 1975-1977, 1980-1983; Box 27, Folders 1-6.
    Arranged chronologically.
    This series contains articles collected by board members of the AAEJ dating from 1975 to 1983.
    - AAEJ Articles, undated, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - AAEJ Articles, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
    - AAEJ Articles, January-May 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - AAEJ Articles, June-December 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - AAEJ Articles, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Series E: AAEJ Release, 1983-1990; Box 27, Folders 7-18.
    The series is composed of the AAEJ's newsletter, titled Release, with issues from 1983 to 1990. The newsletters provide a glimpse of how the AAEJ operated and what they accomplished during the 1980s.
    - Release, Spring 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Release, Fall 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Release, Winter/Spring 1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Release, Summer 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Release, Summer 1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Release, Spring 1986 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Release, Fall 1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Release, Winter 1986 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Release, Spring 1987 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Report from AAEJ 1987: In Review (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Release, Spring 1988 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Release, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Series F: Political Files, undated, 1981-1984, 1986, 1988-1989; Box 28, Folder 1 -- Box 30, Folder 34.
    The series consists of political files. The first subseries contains congressional letters. The second subseries consists of the petitions of President George Bush and Senator Pete Wilson as well as petitions to politicians with letters of support, arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Subseries 1: Congressional Files, undated, 1981-1984, 1986; Box 28.
      The congressional files consist mainly of congressional letters from 1981 to 1984. Also included are congressional districts, congressional projects, a congressional help letter to supports, and fund raising letters to Nate Shapiro.
      - Congressional Districts, Zip Codes, undated, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Congressional Fund Raising Letters to Nate Shapiro, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Congressional Help Letter to Supporters, June 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Congressional - House of Representatives Letter: December 29, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Congressional Letters, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Congressional Letters, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Congressional Letters, January-March 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Congressional Letters, April-June 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Congressional Letters, July-September 1983 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Congressional Letters, October-December 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)